Contato

+5591981348438 (Mobile) andre.def93@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ andredefremont (LinkedIn) defremont.github.io (Personal) amachains.com.br (Company)

Principais competências

Blockchain

Vue.js

Progressive Web Apps (PWA)

Languages

Francês (Limited Working)
Inglês (Full Professional)
Português (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

Semana OminiStack 11

C# - CSharp Básico

Gestor de Marketing Digital e Mídias Sociais

PNL - Programação Neuro Linguística

NASA Space Apps Challenge Brazil 2020

Andre Defremont

Blockchain Developer (C.I.O) @ Amachains Belém

Resumo

Bachelor in Information Systems, worked for a company that provided services and systems to public and private companies (.NET, C#, HTML, CSS, JS, SQL). The experience for about 6 years, enabled me to know several systems, languages and parallel knowledge as Digital Marketing Consultant, Social Media and Web Design.

I worked remotely in 2016 at LEAPFORCE with evaluation research for various companies like Facebook, I stayed the maximum contract time per project and excellent productivity.

Experience with mobile applications (IONIC, JAVA) and value the continuous improvement of UX / UI in my projects because I know that this is the differential that we can get in our services. I work constantly with web projects (Wordpress, Angular, HTML, JS, CSS, MERN, Dapps, Blockchain, Hyperledger) and I like to contribute in other projects with my skills and knowledge.

I am currently focusing on Blockchain technologies for databases and highly interactive interfaces with new features and front end frameworks:

- Hyperledger
- Docker
- NodeJS
- React / Vue.js / Angular

Let me know if you have some proposal that fit in my skill and knowledge. Also check my portfolio for details about some projects, and contact-me.

defremont.github.io | github.com/defremont | andre.def93@gmail.com

Experiência

Amachains

Diretor de informações

junho de 2019 - Present (1 ano 4 meses)

Belém e Região, Brasil

- Blockchain Network
- AWS / EC2 / Kubes
- Vue.js
- Angular 7/8
- Hyperledger

Equilibrium_Web

Software Developer

julho de 2019 - março de 2020 (9 meses)

Belém e Região, Brasil

- Angular 4/5
- Java
- JSF
- SpringBoot
- Ionic

Xifix

Monitoring and Developer Analyst abril de 2018 - julho de 2019 (1 ano 4 meses)

Belém, Pará

- UI/UX experience
- Clean design
- React.js / Redux

Universidade Federal do Pará

Web Developer

janeiro de 2017 - janeiro de 2018 (1 ano 1 mês)

Belém e Região, Brasil

Responsible for the planning and development of an innovative look for the former portal of a college institute.

- CSS HTML JS
- Joomla
- PostgreSQL

Agência Digital CastleDev Sócio e Gerente de Marketing 2013 - 2018 (5 anos)

Belém e Região, Brasil

Onbyte

Digital Marketing Developer and Consultant junho de 2012 - julho de 2016 (4 anos 2 meses)

Belém e Região, Brasil

- CSS HTML, JS
- React.js / Redux
- Node.js

Barsa Planeta

RCA - Representante Comercial Autônomo julho de 2011 - agosto de 2011 (2 meses)

Parauapebas/PA

Formação acadêmica

Universidade Federal do Pará

Bacharelado em Sistemas de Informação, Blockchain · (2013 - 2017)

Universidade Rural da Amazônia

Licenciatura em Computação · (2012 - 2013)